You three, don't move!
Don't go near the water!
Don't even try to play tricks on us.
I know one of you
did this to us!
The one who killed the guard
and just tried to drown us,
I know she's among you.
We absolutely have to find
the murderer right now,
or we're all done for!
What are you talking about?
Don't move, I said.
Atroe said
she didn't recognize you.
And you two?
Do you remember her
from the assembly?
I don't remember you either.
You know perfectly well
I've been here since the start.
I don't remember your face.
What?
We don't remember
you either, bitch.
I'm the one who just
made that radio call.
It might be a trap of yours.
Wait.
The black-haired one,
your nose is bleeding.
What the...
I couldn't see it from where I was.
Hermes, when you struck
the enemy Stand,
someone almost passed out.
Get back.
Get away from the water.
You've got it all wrong!
This bitch just hit me!
Look, she's bleeding too!
Damn it.
Her tooth scraped my arm!
I've been here from the start, damn it.
Only these two are left
as suspects.
Listen to me. I saw the warden
with his alligator puppet.
I remember you two as well.
You were the one acting up over there.
That's right.
You're as suspicious as...
Jolyne!
Is this bitch the one who attacked us?
How did you figure it out?
Honestly, I have no idea
who the murderer is.
So I'm going to hit everyone!
You...
You bitch!
She...
I was planning to finish them off
one by one in the water.
Who would have thought
she had that thread
and would survive our attack?
Who are these chicks?
Did they all kill him?
What's going on here?
Who is the Stand user?
You're mistaken.
There is one user
for each Stand and each power.
The ones who were there from the start
are the black-haired one
and the short-haired one.
I killed them
because they were getting close to the tractor.
Then I digested
their bodies and their minds.
This body, I created it...
from the limbs of the missing inmates.
The black sludge comes from the two bodies.
My divided parts
reunited into one.
For the power and the intelligence
that Whitesnake's discs
granted me,
I will defend myself at all costs.
It is my duty
to eliminate anyone who gets
close to the barn.
Damn it.
Where is this Stand's user?
You don't understand, Hermes.
 He is the Stand's user.
 What?
He's alive.
He's a living creature
that received life and power
through the discs.
The guardian of the discs wasn't human.
A living creature?
You mean a conglomerate
of those tiny little bastards?
He must be using
the water from his victims' bodies
to move on dry land
and guard the barn.
He stays on land by multiplying.
But just like a car
needs gasoline,
he needs water to live.
We'll only be able to retrieve the discs
by keeping this creature
away from the water
and reducing it to nothing!
But, Jolyne,
how could a swarm of vermin
be able to speak?
Foo Fighters!
When you talk about me,
use my name!
An astronomer named Fred Hoyle
once said
that it's statistically false
to claim life appeared on Earth
by pure coincidence.
A power called intelligence
existed in the universe
long before the Earth was formed.
It gave birth to life.
Intelligence has existed
longer than the Big Bang.
Every particle, every organism,
contains intelligence.
What is this
bullshit now?
He's saying our intelligence
isn't specifically human.
Even plankton has memory, and...
I told you to call me Foo Fighters!
I am a being of intelligence
superior to yours!
This sucks.
He's going to try to hide the discs
before we find them.
If he buries them,
our chances are over!
Jolyne, there's a big problem.
Look behind you.
It's the creature
that attacked us in the water.
He's trying to drag the guard's body.
Our bracelets, remember.
We have to stay within 50 meters of him.
It's over, Jolyne.
We have to give up on the discs.
We have to take
the guard's body back!
Otherwise, our bracelets will explode.
You handle the bracelets, Hermes.
What?
While I run the 50 meters,
you get the guard's body
and bring it within 50 meters
of me.
 It's the only solution.
 Hey, wait!
What a woman.
She's completely nuts!
What does she want me to do?
Oh, damn it.
If he gets the guard's body,
it's over for Jolyne and me.
I have to act now!
I made it, damn it.
But I'll never use
the sticker like that again.
I won't have another arm
pushed out of me again.
I'll have to juggle, damn it.
And now,
within 50 meters of the barn.
The water.
You damn little worms!
That scream...
You think you've won?
Here's the original corpse,
dried to the bone.
There's not a trace of moisture left in it.
My sticker doubled it.
When I remove the sticker...
You absorb water
like a sanitary pad.
Or like a drop of water
falling in the desert.
Shut up! You're in the way!
Get out of there!
Jolyne.
We have to dehydrate him.
That's the only way
to beat these bastards.
You're right on time.
Either way,
I'm going to kill you both.
I wanted to torture you
after hiding the discs.
But that doesn't matter.
I have a question.
Are you going to jump into that puddle?
Or are you going to try to run away?
Which death do you prefer?
I have questions too.
The one who knows who you are.
Is it Whitesnake?
And also...
what is his goal?
Why does he collect the discs?
Very interesting.
I understand the logic
of offensive defense.
Fighting for an ally
doesn't resonate much with me,
but it seems reasonable too.
However, I don't understand
why you want to die here.
Whitesnake, huh?
Who knows? I've never met him.
Did you think I was distracted?
That's cheap!
All these puddles
are extensions of myself!
You were planning to open this sack of flour
to absorb the water?
Whatever you do,
I know my own power
and I've created the optimal
environment for myself.
It might not be so bad
to use your body
as a host for a while.
No.
You've already lost.
This environment you created for yourself
by splashing water everywhere
will be your downfall.
You didn't even hear me
start the tractor with my threads.
The noise was covered by the sound of the water.
You let yourself get distracted trying to kill me.
And now,
you've failed to guard the discs.
You... Bitch!
You won't get them!
These discs are mine!
The soil of this field is much softer
than that of the swamps.
And it absorbs all the water.
And there's no shortage of water!
I won't let you lay a finger
on these discs...
Jolyne won the battle of minds.
The discs no longer belong to you.
You're finished!
Dry up and feed the crops!
Jolyne.
 Jolyne, what the hell are you doing?
 I'm giving him water.
We can just say
that I'm saving him.
 What?
 Foo Fighters
He wasn't guarding the discs
out of loyalty to Whitesnake.
I'm certain of it.
Even though he knew
his body was going to perish,
he went after the discs.
He was guarding the discs
to protect himself.
The discs gave him
power and intelligence.
If he wanted to protect them,
it was to thank them
for the miracle that was his life.
He couldn't care less about Whitesnake.
You want to save him?
He killed five people!
He's literally not human!
If he's not human,
then he doesn't understand
the concept of evil.
Whitesnake is the villain.
Whitesnake only gave him
enough information
to guard the discs.
 Well, I'll be...
 Besides,
I have another reason
to save his life.
I'll make you a deal.
The discs,
I want you to keep guarding them.
But do it for us.
Protect them
from Whitesnake's dirty hands.
I have no intention
of taking these discs from you.
I only want my father's.
And I want to know
what Whitesnake is up to.
So? Will you help us?
But no more killing humans.
Damn.
You're really something.
I don't quite understand you,
but I don't feel like fighting anymore.
I've lost anyway.
I'm wiped out.
So the discs really were
in the tire!
We finally found them!
Here's Star Platinum!
Jolyne!
Are you okay? Hey!
No doubt about it.
This is the Star Platinum disc.
My father, Jotaro Kujo,
can be brought back to life with it.
I finally have it!
But no trace of his memory disc.
Where could it be?
Hey!
If I jump out this window,
do you think I'll die?
That's me!
F.F. Call me that.
I collected what was left of her.
I added another inmate's
bracelet.
I want to use this body as a host
for a while.
This hand is useless, though.
You want to take her life from her?
You mean
you'll live in her cell,
as a prisoner?
Jolyne,
I want to protect you.
According to this body's memory,
her name is Atroe.
Inmate FE39423.
Her childhood dream was to be kidnapped.
But when she grew up,
she kidnapped a child.
It wasn't for a ransom.
She doesn't know why she did it.
Hey...
Your arms are bleeding.
Does it hurt?
Sadly, I can't heal them.
 Damn it, what are you doing?
 That's gross!
Water!
You should wait a bit
before going back to prison.
Don't you want to learn
to drink from a glass first?
From a glass?
Child's play!
Drinking from a glass, too easy.
Blech.
By the way, about Whitesnake.
Does he come to the barn often?
No, rarely.
I've never seen his user.
The discs that are here
are the ones he can't use.
If there's an incompatibility,
the body rejects the disc,
no matter how powerful it is.
All these discs are ones
he can't use.
He must be hiding
the important discs somewhere else.
That's why
the memory disc you're looking for
isn't in this pile.
What he wanted to tear from your father
wasn't an invincible Stand.
It was his memory.
Your father must know
some secret information.
Secret...
The guards are coming.
What are you going to do, Jolyne?
You have the Star Platinum disc.
Now,
I'm going to give this to the foundation
that takes care of my father.
If I don't revive him soon,
his body will start to rot.
I'll find his memory disc
no matter what.
Get it out of the prison.
It's harder to get things out of here
than to bring them in.
And the guards are going to
strip-search us.
Let me see that disc.
I'm going to shape my boobs.
F.F., raise your hands,
or they'll shoot you.
You too, Hermes.
The guard was attacked by an alligator.
We saved him.
We don't know what happened
to the other inmates.
We stick to that story, okay?
She was nothing but bait.
Jolyne was only supposed to lure Jotaro.
I thought she'd be harmless.
Jolyne Kujo.
She defeated the guard all by herself
and retrieved the discs?
Did the surviving inmates
help Jolyne?
The sun will set soon.
You must return
to your quarters.
Are you that worried
about the missing ones,
Father Pucci?
One moment, please.